Welcome back again with yet another Zack
Toys mini figure review and today we're
going to be taking a look at the brand
new ish McFarland Toys Bronze Tiger.
Now, this isn't a character I was
clamoring for but I think he's a good
addition to your Suicide Squad or just
your generic Batman villains. Um
but this isn't a great figure. I mean
he's got some new sculpted parts, new
belt, new hands and a new head. Most of
it's Grifter but that new head is just
I don't think I like it very much. I
would have much like preferred it to
look like the character but the
articulations also kind of ass. The
accessories are weak like it's just an
outdated figure from a line that is just
seemingly jumping ship at this point. I
mean McFarland just is kind of becoming
desperate at this point to get out as
much as they can in as little amount of
time as possible because they don't have
the license anymore and this is just
kind of one of those examples.
It's not awful
but it definitely could have been a lot
better. So, I don't know. What do you
guys think?